EPISODE 9
（第 9 集）
-Tastes just right. -By the way, where is it?
-味道剛剛好 -對了，東西在哪裡？
The guardian stone and the golden ruler.
守護石和金尺
I'm only asking because I'm worried.
我只是因為擔心才問的
They'll be rushing in any day now.
他們隨時都會衝進來
Red-white mask and the Governor-General. I'd hate to get caught up in all that.
紅白面具人和總督 我可不想被捲入這些麻煩
Fine. I'll leave Myoyeongak with the stone and the ruler, then.
好吧，我會帶著守護石和金尺 離開妙緣閣的
So… where did you put it?
那麼…東西放哪去了？
You…
你…
hid those in my room?
居然把它藏在我的房間裡？
Is there a safer place in Myoyeongak?
放眼整個妙緣閣 還有比這更安全的地方嗎？
Can you give that to me?
可以把它給我嗎？
My time travel started…
我的時間旅行…
with this guardian stone.
是從這塊守護石開始的
Hong-joo, I can't go home without this.
紅酒，沒有它，我就回不了家
That's why I will wipe out anyone who gets in my way.
所以誰敢擋我的路，我就消滅誰
-Even me? -Even you.
-甚至包括我在內？ -沒錯
Can you handle it?
你下得了手嗎？
I'm going to the Bando Hotel.
我要去坂東飯店了
Either Moo-yeong or the Governor-General,
無影也好，總督也好
tell whoever wants this that I'll be at the Bando Hotel.
轉告想要這東西的人 我在坂東飯店等他們
Because I don't intend to hide or run.
因為我沒打算躲起來或逃跑
Hey, Moo-yeong.
千無影
You seem well, drinking in dire times.
很悠哉嘛，大難臨頭了還在喝酒
Lee Yeon, how are you here?
李硯，你怎麼會來這裡？
Enough of that. Let's give you a beating first.
夠了，先揍你一頓再說
You bastard.
你這個混蛋
Gosh, damn it.
天哪，該死
How does it feel?
感覺如何？
How does it feel to beat each other with these hands we once used
用這雙曾經互相扶持的手毆打對方
to support each other with?
感覺怎麼樣？
You here to preach?
你是來說教的嗎？
I'm here to see how I'd feel doing this. It's not as refreshing as I imagined.
我想來試試這樣做會是什麼感覺 結果沒有我想得那麼爽
That makes two of us.
我也很不爽
Just pour me a drink.
給我倒杯酒
-What? -For your information,
-什麼？ -你要知道
I didn't bring the treasures you're looking for.
我沒把你想找的寶物帶在身上
Safety comes first.
安全第一
-You have a guest, sir. -Who is it?
-總督，有客人來了 -是誰？
It's been a while, demons.
好久不見，妖怪們
To what do I owe the pleasure of having Myoyeongak's Madame here?
是什麼風把妙緣閣閣長吹來了？
I hear four new kids are sweeping the Gyeongseong grounds.
聽說有四個新來的傢伙正在掃蕩京城
-They're called Shinigami. -Shinigami?
-他們是死神 -死神？
Which means the god of death?
專門取人性命的嗎？
Gosh, I don't like it.
天哪，我不喜歡
But why come to me instead of paying them a visit?
但是妳不去找他們，來找我做什麼？
-Well, you brought them here. -Oh, my.
-是你把他們叫來的 -哇
You truly are the most informed in Joseon.
不愧是朝鮮消息最靈通的人
What do you want?
妳想怎樣？
Mercenaries or whatever. I'm not interested in all that.
我不管他們是不是僱傭兵團 我對那些不感興趣
You're looking for the treasures, aren't you?
你在尋找寶物對不對？
If I help you get them, what will you give me in return?
如果我幫你拿到它們 你會如何報答我？
-What is it you want? -Don't mess with Myoyeongak, or my girls.
-妳想要什麼？ -不要傷害妙緣閣和我手下的女孩子
So you're willing to join hands with me to protect Myoyeongak?
為了保護妙緣閣，妳願意與我聯手？
So much for a mountain god of Joseon.
朝鮮山神也不過如此
I never start a losing fight.
我從來不打沒有把握的仗
I'll ask you just once.
我只問你一遍
You in or out?
要不要合作？
You plan to revive your brother with the treasures?
你打算用寶物復活你哥哥？
-You crazy fool. -Didn't your brother die in the year 2020?
-瘋子 -你弟弟不是死在了2020年嗎？
If you had those items then,
假如你當時擁有那些寶物
-what choice would you have made? -I would've been tempted.
-你會選擇怎麼做？ -我會忍不住心動
But I'd make the same decision if I were to face that moment again.
但如果讓我再次面對那一刻 我依然會做出同樣的決定
I'd wait for him to reincarnate, and fight to gain virtue.
我會等待他轉世，為道德而戰
That's nothing new to me.
又不是第一次了
You always play by the book.
你老是這麼守規矩
But that's exactly why I became a mountain god.
我就是因為這樣才能成為山神啊
I don't cross the line at any cost.
無論如何，我都不會越界
Say you turn into stone, neither alive nor dead for centuries.
如果是你被變成石柱 不死不活幾百年
Then, that sort of crap is useless.
我看你還說不說得出這些風涼話
You chose that path.
那條路是你自己選的
If you break the taboo and annihilate an entire mountain,
既然要打破禁忌，毀滅整座山的生靈
you should be prepared to pay.
就應該準備好付出代價
-I am prepared. Back then and now. -That's what matters.
-我準備好了，無論當年還是現在 -這才是最重要的
Do your best to take the guardian stone and the golden ruler from me.
使出全力 從我這裡奪走守護石和金尺吧
And save your brother.
然後去救你哥哥
I'll risk my life to protect the treasures and fight against you.
我會拚命保護寶物，與你對抗到底
So today's the last time…
所以今天是我們最後一次…
we drink together.
一起喝酒了
Thanks for the drinks.
謝謝你的酒
-I'm going to the Bando Hotel. -Let me ask you one thing.
-我要去坂東飯店了 -我問你
What was I to you?
你當初是怎麼看待我的？
As you know, I was a perverse kid.
你也知道，當年的我是個任性的小孩
So self-centered too.
只會以自我為中心
You taught me how to fight to protect someone.
是你教會我為保護別人而戰的
I wanted to be a mountain god like you.
我想成為像你那樣的山神
How funny. You always seemed to shine back then.
真好笑，當年的你總是那麼耀眼
You were fearless and always made your own decisions.
勇敢無畏，總是自己做決定
You… were my dream.
曾經的你…是我的夢想
I guess that's why we were friends.
所以我們才能做朋友啊
I'll get going.
我先走了
-Will you hand over the treasures? -Do you think I'm out of my mind?
-閣長要交出寶物嗎？ -你以為我瘋了嗎？
The treasures are mine.
寶物是我的
-Then why cooperate with him, ma'am? -I'm trying to buy some time.
-那閣長為什麼和他合作？ -我想爭取一些時間
I want him to sit tight while I take the treasures.
希望他在我拿到寶物之前按兵不動
-Do you think he fell for it? -No.
-閣長認為他有上當嗎？ -沒有
He's stronger and cleverer than expected.
他比我想像中更強大、更聰明
-I might even take a hit. -Are they worth all that trouble, ma'am?
-我有可能會慘敗 -閣長，他們值得妳這樣冒險嗎？
Is it worth antagonizing the governor, involving Lord Lee Yeon and--
值得妳得罪總督嗎？ 就為了李硯大人和…
Jae-yoo, say I get my hands on them.
載宇，假如我拿到寶物
Then, Yeon can't go home.
阿硯就回不了家了
If all else fails,
如果其他計劃都失敗
we will leave this dreadful era with the guardian stone,
我們就帶著守護石 離開這個令人痛苦的時代
and run off to a new world.
逃往一個新世界
So starting now…
所以，從現在起…
let's enter the eye of the storm.
就讓我們走進暴風眼吧
Father.
爸爸
Where have you been?
妳去哪裡了？
I got some clothes at the department store. Oh, right.
我去百貨商店買衣服了，對了
I also got a tie for you.
我還幫爸爸買了一條領帶
Good. I'll wear that to your wedding.
好，我會戴著它參加妳的婚禮
My wedding? What are you talking about?
我的婚禮？什麼意思？
Get married and quit being a reporter.
嫁人吧，不要再做記者了
Whom will I marry?
我要嫁給誰？
Your brother-in-law. The ceremony will be this Sunday.
妳姊夫，婚禮定在這個週日
That's insane. You must've lost your mind, Father.
瘋了，爸爸，你瘋了吧
Sis killed herself after getting married to him!
姊姊嫁給他之後就自殺了！
Answer me.
回答我
The day the commander died in the Gyeongseong Station bombing,
指揮官在京城站爆炸案中身亡那天
where were you?
妳在哪裡？
Answer me!
回答我！
Don't you already know?
你不是已經知道了嗎？
You're right. I was there.
沒錯，我是在那裡
If only I had both my daughters… I wouldn't have missed.
如果我的兩個女兒都活著 我是不會打偏的
Honey, honey, please! Please, let's talk instead!
老公，求求你！有話慢慢講！
No activists are welcome in my house!
我們家不歡迎獨立份子！
Why did you do it?
妳為什麼要這麼做？
We did everything for you, and yet-- The independence movement?
我們所做的一切都是為了妳，而妳呢 居然參加獨立運動？
He's mistaken, huh? Tell me it's not true!
是他弄錯了對不對？ 告訴我這不是真的！
Sorry, Mother.
對不起，媽媽
Ginko.
銀子
I'm not Ginko.
我不是銀子
My name is Sunwoo Eun-ho.
我叫鮮于恩好
Are we getting anywhere?
有進展嗎？
There are no survivors yet. The longest to endure was about two days.
目前還沒有存活下來的 最長的忍耐時間是兩天左右
All their eardrums burst, so…
他們的耳膜都有破裂，所以…
-Is it due to the gwiso tree? -Yes, sir.
-是因為歸巢木嗎？ -是的
GWISO TREE A HAUNTED WHISTLING TREE
（歸巢木：一種會發出哨聲的鬼樹）
WHERE THOSE WHO HEAR IT GO MAD
（聽見的人會發瘋）
Injecting them with the sap of this tree messes with their heads.
給他們注射樹液會擾亂他們的心智
The problem is that they die when they hear the whistles, no?
問題是他們聽到哨聲會死掉吧？
I apologize, sir.
是我無能，長官
If you don't obtain good results, the next test subject…
如果你拿不出令人滿意的結果 下一個試驗對象…
will be you, Akira.
就是你，阿亮
I will definitely make it a success, sir!
我一定會成功的，長官！
Did you call for us?
你找我們嗎？
You have a new mission. Bring me the nine-tailed fox's treasures.
你們有一項新任務 幫我拿到那隻九尾狐的寶物
Can I bring you the treasures and keep the nine-tailed fox perhaps?
寶物歸你，九尾狐可以歸我嗎？
She's speaking nonsense, sir.
她只是在胡說八道，長官
You saw him up close. What was he like?
你近距離觀察過他 他是什麼樣子？
He uses his head like a well-oiled machine.
他的腦筋轉得飛快
He was fighting a losing battle, but he turned the tables in an instant.
明明是註定輸掉的賭局 他瞬間便翻盤了
He is a mountain god of Joseon.
他是朝鮮山神
You think you can handle him?
你有把握對付他嗎？
Leave it to me, sir.
交給我吧，長官
-He'll be going to the Bando Hotel. -Yes, sir!
-他接下來要去坂東飯店 -是！
You dare summon the owner of the Stream of the Dead?
你竟敢召喚三途川的主人？
Have a bowl of naengmyeon.
吃碗冷麵吧
Here, try some.
來，嚐嚐看
What do you think?
怎麼樣？
It's nice and refreshing, but…
美味爽口，但是…
What is your motive?
你有什麼企圖？
Japanese demons are wiping out our indigenous gods.
日本妖怪正在屠殺我們的本土神
You think my thousand-mile eyes are just for decoration?
你以為我的千里眼只是擺設嗎？
Let's be honest. You're frustrated too, aren't you?
坦白講，妳也覺得很挫敗吧？
You hate that you can only watch as the invaders turn everything to ruins, no?
妳討厭眼睜睜看著侵略者 將一切變為廢墟的感覺，不是嗎？
We do not interfere in human affairs.
我們不干涉人類事務
That is the rule.
那是規矩沒錯
But, like you said, I don't belong here.
但是妳親口講過，我不屬於這裡
I'm just a traveler passing through this era.
我只是這個時代的過客
What are you planning now?
你又在打什麼算盤？
I'm going to kill all the Japanese demons before I go home.
我要在回家之前殺死所有的日本妖怪
You only need to hush yourself until you return, but how--
你明明只要安安靜靜地 等到回去的那一天就好，但你怎麼…
It's something only I can do. And something I should've done before.
這件事只有我能做 而且是我以前就該做的
I have a debt to settle in this era, old hag.
老妖婆，我欠這個時代一筆債
I'll take that as a "yes."
我就當妳答應了
Is this it?
就是這個嗎？
The reason my future self sent Yeon to this era.
未來的我將阿硯送來這個時代的原因
Gosh. It's almost time to say farewell to this landscape too.
天哪，我就快要和這番景色說再見了
D-4 DAYS
（倒數計時，四天）
You're suddenly going to a hotel? What about me?
你突然要去飯店住？那我怎麼辦？
-You don't need to come. -What?
-你不用去 -什麼？
Everyone will swarm to the place for the guardian stone and golden ruler.
所有人都會湧向 守護石和金尺所在的地方
It's safer to stay away from me for now.
你暫時遠離我比較安全
-Damn it. -You're so annoying.
-真是的 -你好煩
You also looking down on me because I'm a half-fox?
你也瞧不起我這隻半狐嗎？
-Me? -Then, why don't you turn to me once?
-我有嗎？ -那你為什麼從來不找我幫忙？
I want to. I'd like to depend on you too.
我也想啊，我也想依靠你
But you're my only weakness here.
但你是我在這裡唯一的軟肋
If you get hurt again, I will lose it this time.
如果你再次受傷，我會徹底瘋掉的
I'm not the kid you used to piggyback.
我已經不是要你背在身上的小孩了
The least you can do is let me decide my own path.
你至少應該允許我選擇自己的道路吧
You don't have much time left, no? Don't regret it later on.
你所剩的時間不多了對不對？ 不要等以後再後悔
Fine, let's go together. You stick right next to me.
好吧，我們一起去，寸步不離
-All right! Let me go! -Lord Lee Yeon!
-好了！放開我！ -李硯大人！
-Go away! -Yeah?
-走開！ -啊？
How nice.
真好
-She says to have a farewell party. -Hong-joo?
-她說要舉辦一場送別會 -紅酒嗎？
Yes, and this is for you.
是的，這是給你的
-Information on the Japanese demons. -Right.
-關於日本妖怪的情報 -好
-Why me? -I picked you to marry from the start.
-為什麼是我？ -從一開始，我選擇要娶的人就是妳
But your sister brought it on herself, when she said she'd marry me instead.
但是妳姊姊主動獻身 說要代替妳嫁給我
I don't know where, and what rumor she heard,
我不知道 她從哪裡聽到了什麼樣的傳言
but she already knew
但她早就知道
that I'm not one of the good guys.
我不是什麼好人了
That's why she married you in my place?
所以她決定代替我嫁給你嗎？
Perhaps she wanted to protect her only sister, though…
也許她想保護唯一的妹妹，可是
she couldn't protect her own life.
她連自己的性命都保護不了
You killed her, huh?
是你殺了她對不對？
Well, your sister saw things she shouldn't have.
妳姊姊看到了不該看的東西
That's why she died.
所以才會死
I'll kill you!
我要殺了你！
A new bride shouldn't be carrying guns.
新娘不該隨身帶槍的
I won't marry you to save my life.
我不會為了活命嫁給你的
But you will.
妳一定會的
What's with the long face?
怎麼看起來悶悶不樂？
-I got cut before the preliminary rounds. -How come?
-我在預賽前就被淘汰了 -怎麼會？
A gisaeng from Pyongyang, and an actress who models for some soap, got picked.
一位平壤妓生和一位肥皂劇女演員 被選中了
But they said they wanted a singer…
他們明明說要歌手的…
-Get in. -I don't feel like watching a movie.
-上車 -我不想看電影
Let's go see something else, then.
那我們去看看別的
Wow, it's the ocean!
天哪，是大海！
It's been so long since I've smelled the ocean.
我太久沒有聞過大海的氣味了
You like it that much?
妳有那麼喜歡海嗎？
I missed it.
我想它了
So much that I even heard the sound of waves in my dreams.
甚至會在夢裡聽到海浪的聲音
How did you think to bring me here?
你怎麼會想到帶我來這裡呢？
I may not know much about women, but I felt a mermaid would miss the sea.
我對女人瞭解不多 但我覺得人魚應該會想念大海吧
Like how I sometimes miss the forest from when I was with Lee Yeon.
就像我偶爾也會想念 我和李硯一起長大的森林一樣
I've forgotten all about getting cut.
我已經把被淘汰的不愉快全忘光了
Let's walk together.
我們一起去散散步吧
Must you really fight?
你真的非得去戰鬥嗎？
Unlike you, I don't like Joseon.
我和妳不同，我不喜歡朝鮮
I don't have many good memories of being born as a half-blood, either.
半人半狐的出身 也沒有留給我什麼美好的回憶
But for the first time, there's something I want to protect on this ravaged land.
但是在這片飽受蹂躪的土地上 我第一次有了想要保護的東西
Then let's fight together.
那我們一起戰鬥
-You can't. -Rang.
-妳不行 -阿朗
If something happens to you, I won't be able to live a single day.
萬一你遭遇不測，我一天都活不下去
I've been on the brink of death countless times.
我曾經無數次站在生死邊緣
And I survived every time.
每一次都活下來了
As long as Lee Yeon's with me, I will never die.
只要有李硯在，我就永遠不會死
That's what it must feel like to have a sibling.
這就是有兄弟的感覺吧
I, too, had a family once.
我也曾經有過家人
I'll be your family, then.
那我來當妳的家人吧
Really?
真的嗎？
Once everything is solved, I'll quit the gang and find a new job.
等一切解決妥當 我會退出土匪幫，換一份新工作
Well, should I just open a record label?
還是我來開一家唱片公司好了？
I'll hold you to that.
講話要算數喔
-What are you asking me to sell? -A Myoyeongak brunch.
-你要我賣什麼？ -妙緣閣早午餐
To increase sales, you must diversify the menu.
為了增加營業額 妳要讓菜單更豐富多樣
Give off a trendy vibe. Offer delivery services too.
打造時髦的氛圍，還要提供外送服務
This is a high-end restaurant.
我們這裡是高級餐廳
In the future where I'm from, even Michelin restaurants deliver food.
在我們未來，連米其林餐廳都有外送
-Who's doing the deliveries? -Yeah, who?
-誰負責送餐？ -對啊，誰去呢？
Use my guys from the bandit gang. They're fleet-footed, you know.
僱用我們土匪幫的手下吧 畢竟他們跑得快
-You're quitting the bandit gang? -It's a thought.
-你要退出土匪幫嗎？ -目前只是想法而已
Wow, I'm so proud. Here, have a drink!
天哪，太感動了，來，喝一杯！
There's a good boy.
真是乖孩子
Who came during the day?
白天誰來過？
-I had a drink with Lee Yeon. -What?
-我和李硯一起喝酒了 -什麼？
To declare war. We've really become enemies now.
是為了宣戰，我們真的變成敵人了
Don't get swayed, Moo-yeong!
別動搖啊，無影！
If that were possible, I wouldn't have come so far.
如果我會動搖的話 就不會走到這一步了
You must kill Lee Yeon and get your hands on the treasures.
你必須殺死李硯，拿到寶物
But Ho-yeong…
可是哥哥…
Back then…
當初
Why did you try to kill me?
你為什麼要殺我？
I told you, I wasn't in my right mind. It was all Taluipa's doing.
我告訴過你了，我的意識不清醒 都是奪衣婆在搞鬼
To prevent our tiger clan from gaining power.
她想阻止我們虎族得勢
-To annihilate us-- -No, I don't understand.
-想徹底摧毀我們… -我想不通
Taluipa dearly cared for me.
奪衣婆非常關心我
Then, would she have turned you into stone to rot?
那她還把你變成石柱不聞不問？
She needed a hostage from the start. That's why she raised you to be a god.
她從一開始就需要一個人質 所以才把你撫養成神
Okay. I'll retrieve all that we've lost.
我明白了，我會找回我們失去的一切
That's my little brother.
這才是我的好弟弟
I'll bring the guardian stone and the golden ruler.
我會把守護石和金尺帶來的
Move. That's my seat.
讓開，這是我的座位
-What are you doing? -There are seats in the back.
-妳在做什麼？ -你去坐後排吧
Let's go.
出發
Didn't we have a farewell party last night?
我們昨晚不是有開送別會嗎？
I spent all night thinking, and concluded I can't let you go just yet.
我想了一夜，結論是我還不能放你走
-It rips my heart to shreds. -Say that again.
-不然我會心碎 -才怪
What about Myoyeongak?
妙緣閣怎麼辦？
Temporarily closed. Everyone's coming to the hotel.
暫時歇業，大家都去住飯店
I booked your rooms too.
我也幫你們訂好了房間
Let's get going.
走吧
-I'll check us in. Take a look around. -All right.
-我去登記入住，你們隨便晃晃 -好
This looks better than I thought.
這裡看起來比我想像中好一些
-Your name, ma'am? -Don't you know me? It's Ryu Hong-joo.
-女士，您的名字？ -你不認識我嗎？柳紅酒
Four rooms for ten guests, correct?
四個房間，十位客人，對嗎？
I want them all next to each other.
我要全部相鄰的房間
The upper floor looks cool too.
上面一層看起來也很酷
I'm so sorry, sir.
對不起，先生
What's this?
這是什麼？
"The technique of hypnotism"?
《催眠術秘法》？
We're the best hypnotism society in all of Joseon.
我們是整個朝鮮最好的催眠術協會
This book is where our president exposes the secrets of the Heavens.
這本書裡有我們會長洩漏的天機
-Buy me one. -It's all a scam, you brat.
-買一本給我吧 -都是騙人的，臭小子
It's not a scam! If you learn the art of hypnosis,
不是騙人啦！如果你學會催眠術
you can heal all diseases and even communicate with ghosts.
就能治癒所有疾病、和鬼魂溝通
You can even create a thunderstorm in the clear sky.
甚至可以在晴天製造霹靂
-Gosh. -This guy can do that, you know.
-天哪 -這個人真的能辦到喔
-Pardon? -Who would ever believe this stuff?
-什麼？ -誰會相信這東西啊？
Hey, get back to work.
回去工作吧
Stop!
站住！
Geez, you ignorant bastard. It's your damn shoes!
天哪，你這個無知的笨蛋 居然還穿著鞋！
Why are you cursing, all of a sudden?
幹嘛突然罵人啊？
No, I'm telling you. It's your shoes!
不是，我在提醒你，鞋子！
It's good manners to take off your shoes when entering a hotel, you know?
脫掉鞋子進飯店才有禮貌，知道嗎？
I knew that, okay?
我早就知道了
-No, wait-- -Oh, boss! Boss!
-不，等等… -老大！
Damn it.
見鬼
-Why did you take off your shoes? -Is this your first time in a hotel, huh?
-你怎麼脫鞋了？ -你是第一次來飯店吧？
These are proper manners.
這樣才禮貌啦
Look. They're all wearing shoes, except for you.
你看，除了你，所有人都有穿鞋子
-Who told you that? -Koo Shin-ju…
-誰告訴你的？ -具申炷…
Why you sly little-- Come here!
狡詐的混蛋…過來！
Hey, everyone.
大家好
-The fox brothers are in Room 304. -Okay.
-狐狸兄弟住304號房 -嗯
-And you? -Room 301.
-妳呢？ -301號房
See you later, baby.
晚點見，寶貝
Well, she came here determined.
她是鐵了心來的
Don't let your guard down. It will be a bloody night.
別放鬆警惕，今晚會有血雨腥風
The Bando Hotel, please.
送我去坂東飯店
How do I look?
好看嗎？
Yuki is pretty.
宥淇真漂亮
Is that all you can say?
你只會講這句話嗎？
Isn't there anything raunchy and dramatic?
沒有其他放蕩誇張的衣服嗎？
I'm going to a hotel today to meet a freakin' handsome demon.
我今天要去一家飯店 見一個超級帥氣的妖怪
What exactly are you guys?
你們究竟是什麼東西？
What do you mean "what"? We're demons just like you.
什麼“東西”？ 我們和妳一樣，也是妖怪
What is her original form?
她的本體是什麼？
A water snail bride.
田螺姑娘
Water snail bride, what are your talents?
田螺姑娘，妳的天賦是什麼？
Sewing and cooking. That's all.
縫紉和烹飪，僅此而已
Should I drag her out?
要我把她拖出去嗎？
Did I practice singing too much? My throat is burning.
是不是歌練太久了？喉嚨都燒起來了
Ma'am!
店長！
-What's going on? What happened? -I was almost taken by a Japanese demon.
-怎麼了？出什麼事了？ -我差點被一個日本妖怪抓走
A Japanese demon?
日本妖怪？
For the time being, don't go out recklessly.
妳暫時不要隨便出門了
-Where did they go? -They've all flocked to the Bando Hotel.
-他們去哪了？ -全部湧向坂東飯店了
The Bando Hotel? Rang is there.
坂東飯店？阿朗在那裡
I'll be right back.
我去去就回
You can't go!
妳不能去！
Yeo-hee!
汝熙！
Oh, wow!
天哪！
Wow! It's a bed, a hotel bed!
哇，有床，飯店的床！
BANDO HOTEL, ROOM 302
（坂東飯店，302號房）
-Wow. -This hotel!
-哇 -這家飯店好棒！
There's even soap in the room!
房間裡還有肥皂呢！
You think that's all? This room costs a fortune!
妳以為就這樣嗎？這間房間很貴的！
-How much is it? -I'm guessing around a month's salary.
-多少錢？ -我猜大概要一個月的薪水
What's that? Is it kimchi?
這是什麼？泡菜嗎？
Apricot, who brings kimchi to a hotel?
梅花姊，誰會帶泡菜來飯店啊？
I heard they only sell Western food, so I packed some just in case.
我聽說這裡只賣西餐 所以我醃了一些泡菜以防萬一
Gosh, it's not my fault if they treat us like hillbillies.
天哪，如果他們把我們當作鄉巴佬 可不要怪我喔
Hey, hey! This is theft!
喂，這是偷竊！
BANDO HOTEL, ROOM 303
（坂東飯店，303號房）
-My job is to thieve. Let go! -Gosh, what are you doing?
-偷竊是我的工作，放手！ -天哪，你想幹嘛？
Let go. I'm just doing my job.
放手，我只是在做我的工作啦
That's right. Wow!
就是要這樣，耶！
Stop it. That's enough!
住手，夠了！
The painting. Hey, leave me be-- The painting-- Whoa!
還有畫，別管我…畫…哇！
-Oh, why can't I take this off? -Paintings aren't amenities, seriously!
-為什麼拿不下來？ -畫不屬於房間用品，真是的！
-I'll be in the Madame's room. -Jae-yoo, help!
-我去閣長的房間 -載宇，幫幫我！
Hey, you bastard!
你這個混蛋！
Let go. Let go. Let go.
放手…
Hey, don't forget our objective here.
別忘了我們此行的目的
-You think I'm stupid? -Yeah.
-你當我是傻子嗎？ -嗯
Was it right to bring the gisaengs here?
把妓生帶來沒問題嗎？
BANDO HOTEL, ROOM 301
（坂東飯店，301號房）
The Governor-General would've got to them if they knew I left Myoyeongak.
如果總督知道我離開了妙緣閣 一定會對她們下手的
-You all should stay right by me. -What is your plan?
-你們都應該待在我身邊 -閣長有什麼計劃？
I'll snatch the treasure while Yeon and Moo-yeong are fighting.
我要趁阿硯和無影打架的時候 奪取寶物
Until then, you go and have fun.
在那之前，你去盡情享受吧
-What's this? -It's an invitation to our society's--
-想幹嘛？ -我們協會邀請您…
Get lost.
走開
Lee Yeon, it's over now.
李硯，一切都結束了
BANDO HOTEL, ROOM 403
（坂東飯店，403號房）
Nyudo.
入道
Nyudo! Let's hurry and go catch them.
入道！我們快點抓住他們吧
Let's go! Let's go!
加油！
We start work at sundown. Those are the boss's orders.
我們日落開始工作，這是團長的命令
In that case, maybe we should rest while we can?
既然如此 我們現在應該趁機休息才對吧？
Coming in.
進來了
Rang. Do you want to come with me?
阿朗，你想跟我一起走嗎？
-Where to? -Where I come from. The future of Joseon.
-去哪裡？ -我來的地方，未來的朝鮮
There is no gunfire or war there.
那裡沒有槍戰和戰爭
-No Japanese invaders either. -I can't go.
-也沒有日本侵略者 -我不能去
Because of the mermaid lady?
是因為那位人魚小姐嗎？
Be good to that mermaid lady.
好好對待人家
Protect her with your life.
拚命去保護她
A nine-tailed fox's first love is their last and final love.
九尾狐的初戀也是最後的絕戀
All right, here.
這個給你
I wanted to give it to you before I left.
我原本想在離開前給你的
-Rings? -Yes.
-戒指？ -對
It's my wedding gift to you as your brother.
這是哥哥送你的新婚禮物
One for each of you.
你們一人一枚
We have quite a number of uninvited guests.
不速之客真不少啊
I wonder how many of them will make it out alive?
不知道有多少能活著逃掉？
Do I look merciful to you?
你看我像是心慈手軟的人嗎？
D-3 DAYS
（倒數計時，三天）
Gosh, this is so fun. Let's go one more time.
天哪，太好玩了吧，我們再試一次
-Hey, get back in. -I can't-- I just can't.
-回去 -我不行了…不行
-Jae-yoo, what's wrong? -This man right here.
-載宇，怎麼了？ -這個傢伙
He thinks riding elevators is so fun, he's made me ride it ten times!
他覺得搭電梯很好玩 逼我搭了十次！
Look here. He's weaker than he looks.
你看，他沒有看上去那麼壯實
-Are you here for the lecture? -No.
-你們是來聽演講的嗎？ -不是
But you should come.
來聽聽吧
We're giving out free drinks, too.
我們還提供免費飲料
Hypnotism?
催眠術？
They're giving free coffee. Why don't we drink a cup each, huh?
他們提供免費咖啡 不如我們每人喝一杯？
-Let's drink. Drink. -Come in.
-我們去喝吧 -請進
You can sit right over there. There at the end.
你們可以坐那邊，最後面
Whoa, so this is where you all were?
哇，原來妳們都來這裡了？
-The lecture started. -Fine. I get it.
-演講開始了 -好，知道了
HYPNOTISM SOCIETY OF JOSEON
（朝鮮催眠術協會）
Bonjour, mademoiselle. Bonjour, monsieur.
各位先生女士，大家好
Do you know who I am?
你們知道我是誰嗎？
I'm the Hypnotism Society of Joseon's president, Christian Park.
我是朝鮮催眠術協會的會長 克里斯汀朴
I'm glad to meet you all
很高興在這樣的集會上
-at a rendezvous like this. -Bravo.
-見到大家 -好
You are a torchbearer in the Olympics.
你是奧運會的火炬手
Amidst the ardent cheers of the crowd, you appear with the torch…
你在人群的歡呼聲中舉著火炬出現
to relay it right now!
準備接力！
-What? -Oh, wow!
-什麼？ -哇！
Okay, look here.
看吧
As you can see, hypnotism isn't some lousy technique.
大家都看到了，催眠術並非雕蟲小技
It's not magic either.
也不是魔法
It's a medical practice for the psyche all the way from Europe.
它是一種來自歐洲的心理療法
Wow.
哇
All right.
好了
What happened?
怎麼回事？
When you are under hypnotism, you can become anything.
催眠術可以把你變成任何東西
You become someone that you are not!
你會變成另一個人！
-They're all in on it. -What do you know?
-他們都是一夥的 -你懂什麼？
He says it's a new medical practice from Europe.
他說了，這是來自歐洲的新型療法
Now, who wants to try it out for themselves?
現在，誰想親自試一試？
Oh, me!
我！
What should I transform these beautiful mademoiselles into?
我應該把這些漂亮的女士 變成什麼呢？
-Put all your valuables in here, now! -What's all the fuss?
-把你們所有貴重物品放進來，快！ -吵什麼？
I'll cut your throat if I find you hiding anything.
如果敢偷藏，我就割開妳的喉嚨
Honey, call the police!
老公，快報警！
Her brother is a cop, damn it!
她哥哥是警察，該死的！
Boss, you should cut her finger off to set an example.
老大，妳應該砍掉她的手指殺雞儆猴
-You crazy bitches! -Hey, hey!
-妳們這些瘋婆子！ -喂！
Hey, hey! What's wrong? Are you girls drunk?
喂！怎麼回事？ 妳們幾個是不是喝醉了？
-Okay, let's go inside. -Please help!
-好了，進去吧 -求你幫幫我們！
They must be drunk. Sorry about that.
她們一定是喝醉了，對不起
This is our turf.
這是我們的地盤
This isn't the place for the Madame's chick to butt in.
可不是閣長的小白臉插手的地方
-Chick? Huh? -Don't interfere, or else!
-小白臉？ -不准干涉我們的事
-I might just bury you alive. -Hey, got a smoke?
-不然我就活埋你 -喂，你有香菸嗎？
-Say wh-- -You're still wet behind the ears!
-什麼… -妳還是個乳臭未乾的小孩耶！
Can you see it? Can you see if it's still wet or not, huh?
你是看得見嗎？ 你看得出有乾沒乾嗎？
-Oh, my. -I think they've all lost it.
-天哪 -看來她們都瘋了
I can't teach them a lesson either. Just go get Hong-joo.
我又不能教訓她們，去叫紅酒來
-Yes, Hong-joo. -Just wait until she gets here.
-對，紅酒 -乖乖等她過來
-How dare you ask for a smoke! -She's not here.
-妳竟敢向別人要香菸！ -她不在
-Find Jae-yoo. Guys, will you stop! -Jae-yoo. Find Jae-yoo!
-去找載宇，妳們別鬧了！ -載宇，找載宇！
Hey, come out here!
快出來！
Hello?
你好
I'm floating, I'm floating-- Float, float, float!
我要飄起來、飄起來…飄起來！
Are you levitating?
會長有飄起來嗎？
Man, this is weird.
真奇怪
I've hypnotized everyone I've seen today, but how come I can't do this?
我今天見到的每個人都被我催眠了 為什麼我就飄不起來呢？
Maybe you used up too much energy.
也許你今天消耗太多能量了
Whatever the case, I think you're right.
不管怎樣，我覺得你說得對
We could have a good run today, since the hotel's built on expensive land.
這間飯店建在風水寶地 今天的騙局一定會進行得很順利
You must've gotten a spiritual awakening, while scamming everyone.
會長一定是在騙人的時候 出現了靈性覺醒
-I'm floating, floating-- -Yes, you're floating.
-我要飄起來… -沒錯，你要飄起來了
-You're floating, floating. -I'm floating, floating!
-你飄起來了 -我飄起來了！
Did you mess with my henchman?
你是不是對我的副手動手腳了？
Who are you to talk so rudely--
你是誰啊，竟敢如此無禮…
-You prick! -Let's talk!
-混蛋！ -有話好好講！
-Now who the hell are you? -Please, let's talk instead!
-你又是哪根蔥？ -拜託，有話好好講！
-I'm the only son in the family line. -Damn it!
-我是家裡的獨苗 -該死！
Hypnosis or not, just undo it.
不管是不是催眠術，快點撤銷
Wait! Look at this pocket watch closely.
等一下！仔細看我的懷錶
Why? You going to hypnotize me too?
幹嘛？你也要催眠我嗎？
You are now afraid of me.
你現在害怕我
Why would I be?
為什麼？
Since I've taken away your courage through hypnosis. Three, two, one. Bam!
因為我用催眠術奪走了你的膽量 三、二、一，變！
Gosh, seriously?
真是的！
You think that will work on me? Hurry up and undo it.
你以為這對我有用嗎？ 快點把他們變回原樣
Since today's a special day, the hotel's running wild with peddlers.
今天是個特殊的日子 飯店裡到處都是小販
-Peddlers? -Something like that.
-小販？ -差不多
-Are the preparations going well? -You didn't have to come.
-準備工作順利嗎？ -妳不必來這裡的
We're on the same side, no? I'll help you with your treasure hunt.
我們是同一邊的吧？我會幫你尋寶的
No, you stay out of this.
不要，妳別管
I don't like you getting hurt.
我不希望妳受傷
I appreciate your concern, but like I said, don't tell me what to do.
謝謝你的關心 但我講過了，不要命令我
So how do we take the treasures?
我們要怎麼拿到寶物呢？
I doubt Yeon will give it to us without a fight.
阿硯應該不會心甘情願地給我們
I have a plan.
我有個計劃
And what's that?
什麼計劃？
When the sun sets today…
今天日落時…
You heard him, right?
你有聽到他的話吧？
Whatever happens here tonight, stay out of it.
無論今晚發生什麼，你都不要插手
Take care of the girls.
好好照顧女孩們
Can't you take me with you?
閣長不能帶上我嗎？
Don't risk your life so easily.
別輕易拿命冒險
Find someone worth risking your life for.
去找個值得你拿命冒險的人吧
My apologies.
對不起
Excuse me.
不好意思
-Are you here to play? -Our excessive greed caused this disaster.
-你們是來玩的嗎？ -都怪我們太貪心了
That's-- That's right. We were on the lookout for anyone fishy.
沒…沒錯，我們在留意可疑的人
-Just remove the damn makeup. -Quickly. I can't look at you both.
-先把該死的裝扮脫了吧 -快點，你們兩個真讓人看不下去
-Oh, my-- Take them off over there. -Sir.
-天哪…去那邊脫啦 -是
MOO-YEONG - MERCENARIES HONG-JOO - GIRLS - SHIN-JU
（無影，僱傭兵 紅酒，女孩們，申炷）
Let's gather.
大家圍過來
JAE-YOO - LEE YEON
（載宇，李硯）
As expected, everyone's here for the treasures.
不出所料，大家都是衝著寶物來的
Not just the Japanese demons, but also Hong-joo and Moo-yeong.
不僅是日本妖怪，還有紅酒和無影
-Anything on Hong-joo? -She met Lord Moo-yeong earlier,
-紅酒那邊有動靜嗎？ -她之前見過無影大人
and hasn't left her room since.
後來就一直待在她的房間裡
-And Moo-yeong? -He left just now.
-無影呢？ -他剛出去
-To where? -How would I know?
-去哪了？ -我怎麼知道？
The Japanese demons seem to be staying put in their rooms.
日本妖怪似乎在他們的房間裡 按兵不動
Okay, our first target is the Shinigami mercenaries.
好吧 我們的第一個目標是死神僱傭兵團
The Japanese demons wreaking havoc in Joseon these days.
日本妖怪最近一直在朝鮮肆虐
MOO-YEONG 403 - MERCENARIES 404
（無影403，僱傭兵團404）
Room 404.
404號房
I haven't gotten physical in so long.
我很久沒運動了
-No. I do the hunting alone. -What?
-不行，我一個人去狩獵 -什麼？
Research tells me they're quite strong. You can't do it alone.
調查結果顯示他們很強的 你不能單獨行動
And what if the mountain gods chip in?
如果山神和他們聯手呢？
Four Japanese demons and two mountain gods. It's six to one.
四個日本妖怪和兩位山神對付你 等於六對一
That's the real goal of this operation.
這才是這次行動的真正目的
I'm not following at all.
我完全聽不懂
Well, like you just said, the mercenaries are strong.
正如你剛剛講的，僱傭兵團很強大
It might be impossible for me to face the four of them overnight.
我一個人不太可能 在一夜之間對付他們四個妖怪
But what if…
但是如果
Hong-joo and Moo-yeong…
紅酒和無影
side with us?
與我們聯手呢？
What if this becomes
如果這變成
a battle between the mercenaries and the mountain gods?
僱傭兵團和山神之間的戰鬥呢？
They're all going rabid for the items, while Cheon Moo-yeong is out to kill you.
他們都在瘋狂地尋找寶物 而千無影一心想要殺死你
And Madame Ryu's priority is Myoyeongak. She'd never oppose the Governor-General.
柳閣長的優先事項是保護妙緣閣 她絕對不會與總督為敵
How's that even possible?
他們怎麼可能會幫你？
I will make it possible.
我自有辦法
When will you begin?
你什麼時候會開始行動？
When Moo-yeong comes back.
無影回來的時候
You may eat to your heart's content today.
今天妳可以盡情地吃肉了
What--
這…
-Why are you here? -Did you die too, comrade?
-你怎麼來了？ -同志，你也死了嗎？
Well, that's quite a long story.
說來話長
What happened to you?
你遇到什麼事了？
That's not the problem. Comrade Eun-ho is in danger.
這不重要，恩好同志有危險了
She's being forced to marry the Chief Commissioner.
她要被迫嫁給首席專員
-The man from the Government-General? -That man knows everything.
-總督府的那個男人？ -那個人什麼都知道
-You know this man? -No.
-你認識這個人嗎？ -不認識
Stop slacking off and let him in. The dead will come swarming in soon.
別偷懶，快帶他進來 很快就會有大批亡者湧進來了
Yes, honey.
是，老婆
Wear this as you go.
穿著這件衣服走吧
It'll be fairly cold on your way across the Stream of the Dead.
跨越三途川的路上很冷的
Who are you, comrade?
同志，你究竟是誰？
Whoever I may be…
無論我是誰…
It doesn't change the fact that we fought for Joseon together.
我們一起為朝鮮而戰的事實不會改變
My only regret is not seeing the independence of Joseon.
我唯一的遺憾是沒能看到朝鮮獨立
You've had a good run.
你盡力了
Are you crying?
你哭了？
A god that oversees the dead is crying over a human crossing?
監管亡者的神 竟然因為一個人類的死亡而流淚？
I know, right?
是啊
I should be getting used to this by now.
我應該早就習慣了
These are difficult times. For both the gods and the humans.
苦難的時代啊 對神和人類而言都一樣
Still, keep yourself out of it.
但你依然不能插手
Yeon will do it.
阿硯會行動的
What? Yeon will? And you allowed it?
什麼？阿硯？妳允許了？
I doubt the world will turn upside down.
恐怕世界會被攪得天翻地覆
But for once, I want to place my bet.
但是這次，我想賭一把
That Joseon will win.
我賭朝鮮贏
Cheon Moo-yeong is back.
千無影回來了
Shin-ju, go outside now and shut off the electricity at 7:00 p.m.
申炷，你現在出去 在晚上七點準時斷電
-Why? -So the other guests stay in their rooms.
-為什麼？ -那樣，其他客人才會待在房間裡
-The innocent should stay safe. -Sir.
-無辜者不該涉險 -是
And the treasures?
寶物呢？
Here.
在這裡
I just tell the two mountain gods that you wish to see them in Room 404?
我只需要告訴兩位山神 你想在404號房見他們，對不對？
Also, forget about fighting them.
還有，不要跟他們動手
-If you see that happening-- -Okay, I'll avoid them at all costs.
-如果看到情況不對… -知道了，我會竭盡全力避開他們
You.
喂
If your boss gets so much as a nosebleed, I will go berserk.
如果你們老大受傷 哪怕是流鼻血，我都會氣炸的
I understand, sir.
知道了，長官
Lee Yeon wants to see you in Room 404.
李硯約妳在404號房見面
Rang.
阿朗
I looked everywhere for you.
我一直在到處找你
-Why are you here? -The Japanese demons came to the boutique.
-妳怎麼來了？ -那些日本妖怪來洋品店了
What? Are you hurt?
什麼？妳有沒有受傷？
I'm fine, but I heard they all came here.
我沒事，但我聽說他們都來這裡了
I was worried about you, so…
心裡擔心你，所以…
You can't be here.
妳不能待在這裡
No.
糟了
Excuse me.
有人嗎？
They were definitely here.
他們之前絕對就在這裡
They never left this room either.
也始終沒有離開房間
One of them knows how to use the illusion charm, huh?
看來其中一個妖怪會使用幻術
ILLUSION CHARM - CHARM CREATING AN ILLUSION LIKE REALITY
（幻術：製造類似現實的 幻境的法術）
Where are you?
你在哪裡？
You cunning bastard.
狡猾的混蛋
What's with the power outage in such an expensive room?
這麼貴的飯店房間怎麼會停電呢？
What's that noise?
那是什麼聲音？
Apricot, you go ask the concierge to switch our rooms.
梅花姊，妳叫門房幫我們換房間吧
The hallway lights are out too.
走廊裡的燈也不亮了
Excuse me. Is the power out in your room too?
請問一下，妳的房間也停電了嗎？
-Hey, why is it so dark? -Watch your step.
-為什麼這麼黑呀？ -走路小心
Oh, dear.
天哪
President, sir!
會長！
Get off, off!
走開！
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
-Those things respond to noise. -What was that girl just now?
-那些東西是憑聲音攻擊人的 -剛才那個女生是什麼？
A Yacha.
夜叉
The demon that feeds on humans? Why is such a thing in this hotel?
以人為食的妖怪？ 這家飯店裡怎麼會有這種東西？
You will be fine.
妳們不會有事的
Do not leave this room until I call you.
不要離開房間，等我來叫妳們
-Sir, please wait-- -Move.
-先生，請等… -讓開
What's that? You okay, miss?
那是什麼？小姐，妳沒事吧？
What on earth is that monster?
那個怪物究竟是什麼東西？
A human that fed on a Yacha's flesh and blood for a fortnight.
被餵食夜叉血肉十四天的人類
With her memories gone, she's like any other Yacha.
人類的記憶已經丟失 她現在和普通夜叉沒有兩樣
-A monster that only thirsts for blood. -Why sacrifice the innocent?
-變成了只渴望鮮血的怪物 -為什麼要犧牲無辜之人？
If Taluipa finds out--
如果奪衣婆發現的話…
I'll deal with that. You didn't know about this, okay?
我會處理的，妳假裝不知道就好
Yeon is in that room.
阿硯在那間房間
Damn it, where are you?
該死，你在哪裡啊？
Gosh, seriously.
真是的
You came alone? Where's Hong-joo?
你一個人來的？紅酒呢？
This forest. Is this your doing?
這片森林，是你變出來的嗎？
Not me, no. The hotel's got some uninvited guests.
不是我，飯店有一些不速之客
Do you even have time for this? Clueless about your brother, huh?
你還有時間在這裡胡鬧？ 你不知道你弟弟的處境嗎？
What did you do to him, huh?
你把他怎麼了？
-I freed a Yacha at the hotel. -A Yacha?
-我在飯店裡放了一隻夜叉 -夜叉？
Your brother must be quite busy now.
你弟弟現在一定很忙
He bumped into his girlfriend as the guests turned into Yachas.
剛撞見了女朋友 飯店客人又紛紛變成了夜叉
-Gosh. How did you become so twisted? -Well, I have nothing to protect.
-天哪，你怎麼會變得這麼扭曲？ -我不需要保護什麼
Hand over the treasure if you want to save your brother.
想救你弟弟就交出寶物吧
-No. -What?
-不要 -什麼？
Though he's a half, he's still a nine-tailed fox.
雖說只有一半血統，他依然是九尾狐
He's not as weak as you think.
沒有你想得那麼弱
Especially with a woman to protect.
何況他還有一個女人要保護
It can't be helped then.
那就沒辦法了
I'm not here to fight you.
我不是來和你打架的
But who cares who I fight first, right?
但是先和誰打都一樣，對不對？
Bring it on.
放馬過來吧
A hibari.
一隻鷚
It's a hibari chirping.
是鷚在叫
What was it in Korean?
韓語叫做什麼來著？
Skylark, you idiot.
雲雀啊，笨蛋
You just had to choose this picture, huh? We can't even see where he is.
你非要選這幅畫嗎？ 我們都看不清楚他在哪
-Lee Yeon must've fell for it, right? -This is the boss's illusion charm.
-李硯一定上當了吧？ -這是團長的幻術
He may be a clever nine-tailed fox, but he won't be escaping this.
即便是聰明的九尾狐也不可能逃出去
Let's go catch the nine-tailed fox.
我們去抓九尾狐吧
Wait for the boss to come.
先等團長來
Hey, can I have one?
可以給我一顆嗎？
We're letting the boss have all the fun? But we waited all day!
要把所有樂趣讓給團長嗎？ 我們都等一整天了！
The target isn't him. It's the treasures he has.
目標不是他，是他身上的寶物
Must we yield such valuables to the Governor-General?
非要把那麼貴重的寶物交給總督嗎？
We have to follow orders.
我們必須遵守命令
Treasures or whatever, I don't care!
寶物什麼的，我都不在乎！
I want to play with the nine-tailed fox!
我要和九尾狐玩！
-I'm telling the boss on you. -So petty.
-我要去團長面前告狀 -真小氣
Ushiuchibo?
牛打坊？
Where are you going?
你要去哪裡？
Number one.
小便
Kids.
孩子們
The treasures are mine.
寶物歸我了
Damn it, really!
該死，真是的！
My goodness!
天哪！
Oh, shit-- Hey, you go that way.
見鬼，你去那邊
What am I, your underling?
幹嘛，我是你的跟班嗎？
You and your complexes.
別再糾結了好不好
Ouch!
哎唷！
Hey, stay down for a while.
你暫時躺一會
-Hey! -Sorry.
-喂！ -抱歉
Hey!
站住！
Hong-joo!
紅酒！
Hey, what's wrong? What is it?
怎麼了？
My leg. I think my leg is broken.
我的腿，我的腿好像骨折了
You're hurt? Where? Your leg or your ank--?
痛不痛？是哪裡？腿還是腳踝…
Our dear Moo-yeong's weakness is me! Sorry about this.
我們親愛的無影的軟肋就是我！ 對不起啦
Thank you.
謝謝
No! Oh, shit!
哎呀，該死！
Damn it.
該死
Damn it! Hey, you little--
該死，妳這個死丫頭…
-Damn it! Whose side are you on? -You just smashed my head with a boulder.
-可惡！你到底站在哪一邊？ -妳剛剛用石頭砸過我的頭
Why the timid attitude, tiger?
老虎，幹嘛畏畏縮縮的？
Hey! Bring it.
喂，放馬過來啊
As if! You really wanna try me, huh?
想得美！ 妳非要考驗我的耐心是不是？
Guys.
兩位
Don't breathe!
屏住呼吸！
-Quit playing games. -Hurry. Look behind you!
-別耍花招了 -快點，看你們身後！
One of them has crawled out at last.
終於有個妖怪鬼鬼祟祟地現身了
Hand over the treasures.
交出寶物
Yeo-hee!
汝熙！
Then I'll spare their lives.
我就會放過他們
You won't die. I won't let you.
妳不會死的，我不准妳死
The mercenaries will come on his call.
僱傭兵團會被他的喊聲引來的
I'll be the bait.
我來當誘餌
-This represents my love. -Hey, hey!
-這代表我的愛 -喂！
The pistil of an iris.
鳶尾花的雌蕊
Will that work?
可行嗎？
It's in the hotel restaurant!
在飯店的餐廳裡！
Now we rattle them from this side.
現在，我們從這邊擾亂他們
Strangely, I have a bad feeling.
奇怪，我有一種不祥的預感
-Are you the boss? -I like you.
-你就是團長嗎？ -我喜歡你
-What? -It means,
-怎麼回事？ -也就是說
I'm a body-switching demon.
我是一個可以交換身體的妖怪
I got you.
抓到妳了
Being a mountain god of Joseon means nothing.
朝鮮山神也不過如此
TRANSLATED BY TIFFANY HWANG
字幕翻譯：鄒琳